[
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, what's in the mouth of the porcelain deer in the Unequalled Reward costume, Porcelain Jade?",
        "answer": "Porcelain Flower"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which animal can make the loudest sound?",
        "answer": "Cachalot"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Penglai Island Domination, what Ancient Beast lives in the Verdant Forest?",
        "answer": "Fox"
    },
        {
        "question": "Where can you buy bonus items in the Penglai Island Domination event?",
        "answer": "Piaomiao Hall"
    },
        {
        "question": "What type of animal is a dolphin?",
        "answer": "Mammal"
    },
        {
        "question": "What's the Perfect Monarch Furniture for the Penglai Island Domination event?",
        "answer": "Fun on Swing"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what's the image of Shang Tong?",
        "answer": "Tiger"
    },
        {
        "question": "How many levels are there to the current Title?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what will happen when 2 White Jade Balls collide?",
        "answer": "25 ingredients around them eliminated"
    },
        {
        "question": "How many times can you fold a piece of paper in half?",
        "answer": "7 times"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what will consume 1 Stamina to start a game?",
        "answer": "Mohist Lodge"
    },
        {
        "question": "What's the title for the No.1 Place of Personal Points in the Mohist Maze Event?",
        "answer": "Brilliant Intellect"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which of the following does not belong to Harem Palace Skins?",
        "answer": "Dynasty on Water"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which animal has the biggest eyes?",
        "answer": "Giant Squid"
    },
        {
        "question": "What color is a giraffe tongue tongue?",
        "answer": "Purple"
    },
        {
        "question": "How many bones does a shark have?",
        "answer": "0"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what will consume 5 Stamina to start a game?",
        "answer": "Mohist Tower"
    },
        {
        "question": "What terrestrial animal has the biggest mouth?",
        "answer": "Hippo"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what's the image of Fa Yi?",
        "answer": "Owl"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, how many initial moves do you have in a game?",
        "answer": "15"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which animal doesn't stand while sleeping?",
        "answer": "Hedgehog"
    },
        {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What is the item turning a selected kind of basic ingredients into another kind?",
        "answer": "Switch Stone"
    },
        {
        "question": "What's the Energy Pill used for?",
        "answer": "Summoning Consorts"
    },
        {
        "question": "At Naddam Fair, who is lost in wealth and fame?",
        "answer": "Natchin"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which Emperor's original image is holding a booklet?",
        "answer": "Xianfeng"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, what does it take to tour the Frontier Market?",
        "answer": "Khata"
    },
            {
        "question": "Which Flower emits no fragrance?",
        "answer": "Dandelion"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which of the following cannot be obtained from Naadam Fair Treasure Shop?",
        "answer": "Chest Rewards"
    },
        {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, what is the Stamina Item called?",
        "answer": "Kumiss"
    },
        {
        "question": "Which of the following cannot be triggered by the Magic Lamp in the Loulan Dominion Event?",
        "answer": "Chest Rewards"
    },
        {
        "question": "What is the biggest bird?",
        "answer": "Ostrich"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whatâ€™s the stamina Pill used for?",
        "answer": "Travel"
    },
         {
        "question": "In a cross-server event, how many times do you need to be the Perfect Monarch before unlocking its Avatar Frame?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
         {
        "question": "Which of the following is relevant to the Porcelain Challenge in the Palace Green Ware Event?",
        "answer": "Eminence"
    },
         {
        "question": "What's the Vitality Pill used for?",
        "answer": "Educating Descendants"
    },
     {
        "question": "What is the Prized Collection of Palace Green Ware?",
        "answer": "Cloisonne Rooster"
    },
     {
        "question": "Which Heroine uses a lance?",
        "answer": "Qin Liangyu"
    },
     {
        "question": "What animal runs fastest?",
        "answer": "Cheetah"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many years can queen bees live?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the item used in the Naadam Fair Treasure Shop for a lottery?",
        "answer": "Rare Agate"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the city first reached in Sea Trade?",
        "answer": "Yunlong City"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many golden grids are there in the Alliance Carnival event?",
        "answer": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what's the lowest rating?",
        "answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many Superheroines does the game have?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "What can you hold in your right hand but never in your left hand?",
        "answer": "Left Hand"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What's the highest rating?",
        "answer": "SSS"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the largest planet in the solar system?",
        "answer": "Jupiter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the first cross-over teleplay IP with CME?",
        "answer": "Young Wong Fei-hung"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following Nations is neutral?",
        "answer": "Cang Wu"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, how many allies can you share Fine Unfired Pottery with?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not an Imperial Battle Pass?",
        "answer": "BP Silver"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the price for a Global Horn?",
        "answer": "50 Gold"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, What encounter will give you stamina?",
        "answer": "Bearer of Ancient Vessels"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following currencies has not appeared in the sea fishing event?",
        "answer": "unflawed"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, what encounters will unlock porcelain Token?",
        "answer": "Great porcelain"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the hardest natural substance?",
        "answer": "Diamond"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following teams is not in the palace cuju event?",
        "answer": "Begonia Flower"
    },
    {
        "question": "what is the event following the appearance of the three simple wooden hammer icons?",
        "answer": "Eureka!"
    },
    {
        "question": "what can't elephants do?",
        "answer": "Jump"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of the following pot is not in the cross-server imperial feast pots?",
        "answer": "Enamel pot"
    },
    {
        "question": "what color is the emerald?",
        "answer": "Green"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of the following consorts doesn\u2019t come from the palace cuju event?",
        "answer": "Su XiaXiao"
    },
    {
        "question": "in the palace green ware event, what determines the nation Rankings?",
        "answer": "Prominence"
    },
    {
        "question": "how many eyes does a bee have?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "which of the following groups doesn't join the porcelain debate in the palace green ware event?",
        "answer": "Imperial Craftsman Group"
    },
    {
        "question": "Up to how many Soulmates can a monarch have at the same time?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, which is the third kiln to be built?",
        "answer": "Zhurong Kiln"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the first Consort you obtained from Stage?",
        "answer": "Fangyi"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware. What is the unique Porcelain showing up in the Porcelain Unearthed encounter Called?",
        "answer": "Enameled Porcelain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Up to how many monarchs can attend the diplomatic feast?",
        "answer": "50"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, which is the fifth kiln to be built?",
        "answer": "Broker\u2019s Kiln"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many countries do the envoys received by the Foreign Ministry come from?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following events can increase Ceramics?",
        "answer": "Defeat Enemy"
    },
    {
        "question": "Up to how many consorts can participate in the haram tea party?",
        "answer": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "What do pandas eat?",
        "answer": "Bamboo"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, what did the foreign envoy bring to compete with your porcelain?",
        "answer": "Iridescent Black Porcelain"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many dragon souls are required to transform an emperor into a true dragon?",
        "answer": "200"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following phases is irrelevant to kiln level in the Palace Green ware event?",
        "answer": "Legendary Craft"
    },
    {
        "question": "What\u2019s the stamina Pill used for?",
        "answer": "Cruise"
    },
    {
        "question": "What\u2019s the name of Lv.1 Realm in the Alliance Realm?",
        "answer": "Niya Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, which is the first kiln to be built?",
        "answer": "Clay Kiln"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, which is the Second kiln to be built?",
        "answer": "Glaze Kiln"
    },
    {
        "question": "What\u2019s the most precious item in the jade for beauty event?",
        "answer": "Empress Crown"
    },
    {
        "question": "What\u2019s the first match for the Sovereign Clash event?",
        "answer": "Bronze Tier"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, which realm doesn\u2019t belong to the kiln Realms?",
        "answer": "Nanyu"
    },
    {
        "question": "When is \u201chunt Kamaitachi\u201d available?",
        "answer": "20:00"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many kiln phases are there in the palace green ware event?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the Emperor\u2019s Base Chibi Image?",
        "answer": "Select Emperor"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following has never appeared in the cross-server imperial feast event?",
        "answer": "Fish"
    },
    {
        "question": "What color is a hippo\u2019s sweat?",
        "answer": "Red"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Loulan Dominion, how many maps are there?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What sweet substance do bees make?",
        "answer": "Honey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following seasonings has never appeared in the let\u2019s BBQ Mini-game?",
        "answer": "Sesame Paste"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Loulan Dominion, how many floors does the Loulan tower have?",
        "answer": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where do dogs sweat through?",
        "answer": "Paw"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal has never appeared in Season icons?",
        "answer": "Cattle"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many grids are there in the Treasure Cave of the Loulan Dominion event?",
        "answer": "25"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the southernmost continent?",
        "answer": "Antarctica"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Loulan Dominion, what\u2019s the avatar frame obtained after becoming the perfect Monarch a certain number of times?",
        "answer": "Desert Shadows"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Prized Collection of Naadam Fair?",
        "answer": "Agate Cup"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the title for the No.1 place at the Naadam Fair?",
        "answer": "Khan of Heaven"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many legs does a spider have?",
        "answer": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, What will begin if the Mongolian King is defeated?",
        "answer": "Treasure Looting"
    },
    {
        "question": "How can negotiate with gods and ghosts and predict death?",
        "answer": "Blessed Shaman"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What's the item increasing your moves?",
        "answer": "Stimulant"
    },
    {
        "question": "Whose illness accounts for the Sea Fishing Event?",
        "answer": "Grand Empress Dowager"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, what is the Stamina Item called?",
        "answer": "Green Gemstone"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the name of Lv.1 Realm in the Allied Nation Dungeon?",
        "answer": "Misty Forest"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, how many same basic ingredients will produce a White Jade Ball after elimination?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Guardian can you get from Wise Monarch Feat?",
        "answer": "Kun"
    },
    {
        "question": "what do koalas eat?",
        "answer": "Eucalyptus Leaves"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is irrelevant to the Palace Green Ware Event?",
        "answer": "Year of Plenty"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, how many kinds of packs can you buy from A Taste of Fine Wine?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, how many exchanges are required to get rewards from the Porcelain Unearthed encounter?",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many lines of defense are there to break through in the Palace Cuju event?",
        "answer": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, What is the Stamina item called?",
        "answer": "Pottery Pack"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Superheroine Consort's original image is holding a fan?",
        "answer": "Mi Yue"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, what does it take to repair a Mysterious Glaze Ware?",
        "answer": "Metal Staple"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who's the girl that took the fatal blow for you in the story stages and died?",
        "answer": "Lin Qing'er"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the name of the highest-phase Kiln in the Palace Green Ware Event?",
        "answer": "Godlike"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Consort's original image has a bird in her hand?",
        "answer": "Guinevere"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, what's the avatar Frame obtained after becoming the Perfect Monarch a certain number of times?",
        "answer": "Master Artisan"
    },
    {
        "question": "At which Nation Level will the Nation Member Quota reach 120?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Curiosity Set doesn't exist?",
        "answer": "Phoenix Adviser"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Palace Green Ware, how many marked Joint Tributes can exist simultaneously?",
        "answer": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, What does the treasure hunt consume?",
        "answer": "The Golden Family Relic"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which cross-server event you have been to the Qihuang Mountains?",
        "answer": "Alliance Carnival"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, what's the Avatar Frame obtained after becoming the Perfect Monarch a certain number of times?",
        "answer": "Boldness of Vision"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Star Consort is related to Shen Zhe?",
        "answer": "An Yun"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the highest mountain?",
        "answer": "Everest"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, what part doesn't grant Khata?",
        "answer": "Treasure Looting"
    },
    {
        "question": "What animal is the highest?",
        "answer": "Giraffe"
    },
    {
        "question": "At Naadam Fair, what determines the Alliance Rankings?",
        "answer": "Mongolian Scimitar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest cat?",
        "answer": "Tiger"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following areas is irrelevant to the Sea Fishing Event?",
        "answer": "Submerged Rocks"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the Prized Collection of Mohist Maze?",
        "answer": "Rectangular Win Vessel"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What will happen when 2 Burr Puzzles collide?",
        "answer": "All ingredients eliminated and point x2"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What's the Avatar Frame obtained after becoming the Perfect Monarch a certain number of times?",
        "answer": "Mohist World"
    },
    {
        "question": "What's the first planet discovered with a telescope?",
        "answer": "Uranus"
    },
    {
        "question": "In Mohist Maze, What's the item turning a basic ingredient into a Burr Puzzle?",
        "answer": "Lucky Gourd"
    }
]
